Juan Pablo Tuttolomondo

Fullstack web developer Systems Analist Bachelor



Systems Analyst Bachelor and full-stack developer, backend -oriented, with experiences in e-commerce applications development, and consumption of external APIs and databases management. Additionally, I have experiences in project management, image processing, and drone piloting that complement my profile.

Skills

- Fullstack developer: Stack PERN /MERN: postgresgl, express, react, node.js.Typescript, python.
- Frameworks/ Librerías: redux, sequelize, MongoDb, Prisma.
- Web: Html, Css tailwind, bootstrap.
- Developping in Genexus.
- Project Management: PMI, Agile, scrum, case studies, Scrum Master. Trello, slack, Discord.
- Versions Control: Git, Github.
- Deployment: Vercel, Heroku, Railway, Aws, Azure web services.
- Image processing: Qgis, Pix4D, Agisoft.
- Drone Pilot B class ANAC licensed .

IT Experiences

- ✓ Sep 2023 Oct. 2023 **Full Stack Developer Munia** <u>Github</u>-Mental and Emotional Health at Work- Objective: Alleviate and improve the mental and emotional health of your collaborators within the work environment. Spain.
 - ◆ Backend development: Databases: Models, queries, Filters, endPoints, APIRestFull, Server, routers, MVC, deployment.<Node.js-Typescript-Prisma-sql-github>.
 - ◆ FrontEnd: <Backend integration /data supports and helps> Ref: <u>Joel Ochoa</u>
- ✓ Mar2023-Ago 2023 Tutor(Teacher assistant) in backend's course (e-commerce full backend) at CoderHouse: Corrections at the students challenges , helpping at teacher's classes . Ref: Alex Pinaida
 - <Javascript, node.js, express, MongoDb, swagger, stripe, jwt, websockets, handlebars, MVC, mock, testing, logging, docker, nest.js>
- ✓ Feb 2023-Ago 2023 **Restautants App**: An app that takes orders from a table, and transfers the order to the kitchen, when the kitchen declares it finished the waiter passes it to the server and the cashier, classifying means of payment and lists of entries/exits. RepoGithub
 - ◆ Backend:<node, Express, MongoDb>
 - FrontEnd:<Vite- React-redux, Html, Css>
- ✓ Jul 2022-Feb 2023 <u>AWAQ</u> ONGD: TEDI group- Ago 2022- Feb 2023 Spain.- Development at <u>institutional</u> site.

 Project Office:Case studies at platform of biological stations Ref.: Jose Serna
 - <php- mySql- Elementor Azure Web Services- MSTeams, Office 365, Trello,Active Directory>
- ✓ Oct 2021-May 2022 <u>Henry</u> Bootcamp: app data consumption from external API,views , filters, queries, data orders <u>Individual Project</u>: API data consumption, <u>Final Project</u>: e-commerce.
 - ◆ FrontEnd: < HTML,CSS,Javascript, React-Redux, Node.js, stripe, Tailwind>
 - Backend:<javascript,node, express, PostgreSql>

Other Experiences

- ✓ 2020-2022 Image Processing: GIS techinician, drone pilot: orthophotogrammetry, contour lines, etc.
- ✓ 2004-2021 Manager- Partner at touristics ventures at Humahuaca-Jujuy- Argentina
- ✓ 2000-2003 Manager- Partner at touristics ventures at Salta Province Argentina
- ✓ 1990-1999 Transmission systems specialist: Radio- optics fibbers-LAN-WAN at Telecom Argentina.

Education

- Excellence Project Management course at AWAQ ONGD, PMP: <u>Jose S.Serna</u> -2022
- FullStack developer at Henry 2022 Drone Pilot B class DOS ANAC License 2021
- Image processing course: NDVI Calculus for presicion agriculture 2021
- Systems Analist BachelorUniversidad Nacional de Salta (UNSa) 2003
- Universitary Computer (UNSa)- 2000
- English level: B1 Intermediate